<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
  xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
  
  <ui:style>
  .text {
    font-family:arial, helvetica;
    font-size: 1.2em;
    text-align: justify;
  }
  .ov_table {
    border: 1px solid #A0A0A0;
    background-color: #E0E0E0;
    width: 99%;
    position: absolute;
    left: 0.5%;
    top: 5%;
    border-radius: 0.5em;
    padding: 10px;
  }
  .section_header {
    font-family: “MS Sans Serif”;
    text-align: left;
    font-size: 2em;
    color: #680000;
  }
  .scrollPanel {
    height: 100%;
  }
  </ui:style>
  
  <ui:with field='res' type='es.erni.demo.client.style.Styles.Resources' />
  
  <g:ScrollPanel styleName="{style.scrollPanel}">
  
  <g:HTMLPanel>
  
      <g:HTMLPanel ui:field="ibimePanel">
        <table class='{style.ov_table}'>
          <tr>
            <td>The Biomedical Informatics Group (<a href="http://www.ibime.upv.es" target="_blank">IBIME</a>) is part of the Institute for Applications of Advanced Information and Communication Technologies (<a href="http://www.itaca.upv.es" target="_blank">ITACA</a> Institute) located at the Technical University of Valencia (UPV), Spain. The Biomedical Information Engineering area (<a href="http://www.ibime.upv.es/bie" target="_blank">BIE</a>) of the IBIME group at the UPV is dedicated to the study and efficient use of information and communication technologies for the management of biomedical information.</td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
            <td>
              <g:DisclosurePanel ui:field="respIbimeDiscPanel">
                <g:header>Responsibilities:</g:header>
                <g:HTMLPanel>
                  <ul>
                    <li>Support and maintenance of Pangea system, the Integration Engine of clinical information at the Consortium General Hospital of Valencia (CHGUV) with a target population of 350000 people. Modified and restructured improving its performance by at least 50% and reduced the cost of maintenance by more than 100%.</li>
                    <li>Development of new modules and functions of Pangea. It involves having a perfect knowledge of Java, Apache Struts framework which honors the Model View Controller pattern, data bases like MySQL, SQL Server, and web application technologies in general. The goal of Pangea is to give an integrated view of the Electronic Health Record of a given patient using standards like ISO-EN13606.</li>
                    <li>Support and implementation of new libraries and modules for the LinkEHR platform. LinkEHR platform is the main product of the IBIME group. It is a software platform for the normalization and semantic representation of clinical data by means of archetypes and Electronic Health Record standards.</li>
                    <li>Management and development of the LinkEHR Integration Engine. It will be a module of the LinkEHR platform that will substitute Pangea.</li>
                    <li>Oversee the development of the EHRflex project. EHRflex is an archetype-based clinical registry system (EHR) independent of a particular reference model. It uses clinical archetypes as guidelines for the automatic generation of web interfaces, oriented to a clinical use and data introduction.</li>
                    <li>System administrator of the IBIME group. The Ibime group had a network of 25 computers along with the servers, which were restructured in order to have a secured network with different services: Samba, HTTP Server, MySQL and SQL Server. Optimized its use using virtualization with VMware.</li>
                    <li>Usability Analyst of the tool “Health Record” for the health system of the Balearic Islands. The project, with a total budget of 6.700.000 €, consisted of Integration and communication between different levels of care, guarantee the quality and security of the clinical data and to improve the ease of use and ergonomics of the applications used everyday by clinicians.</li>
                    <li>Involvement in the project “Modeling clinical information in cancer by archetypes. Clinical, epidemiological and research” of the Clinic Hospital of Barcelona. The objective of the project was to develop a methodology for the specification of structured clinical information in Electronic Health Record (EHR), and to reuse it in different scenarios as registers and biobanks in order to support healthcare, epidemiology and research.</li>
                    <li>Implementation of Interoperability with AVS (Valencian Health Agency) EHR System in the CHGUV (General Hospital of Valencia). The goal of the project is to enable the interoperability between different Care Information Systems in the Valencian Region. Every Hospital must be able to access the web services of the AVS Central Node, and this must be able to access the web services of every hospital as well in order to interchange EHR´s. To accomplish this, Apache Axis 2 and the WS-Security module Apache Rampart will be used.</li>
                  </ul>
                </g:HTMLPanel>
              </g:DisclosurePanel>
            </td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
            <td>
              <g:DisclosurePanel ui:field="achievIbimeDiscPanel">
                <g:header>Achievements:</g:header>
                <g:HTMLPanel>
                  <ul>
                    <li>Pangea is being used successfully for everyday care delivery in CHGUV, becoming the most important computer system for the medical professional who has to access patients´ electronic health records.</li>
                    <li>Successful development of new libraries and modules for the LinkEHR platform.</li>
                    <li>Successful development of LinkEHR Integration Engine. It is supposed to be the most efficient information integration engine, developed with Java using Maven and configured with a graphical tool developed with GWT using the Model-View-Controller pattern.</li>
                    <li>14 Publications in national and international congresses, book chapters and conferences.</li>
                    <li>Learned several technologies that where needed for the study and efficient use of information and communication technologies for the management of biomedical information, such as standards, web applications technologies, Web Services technologies, Software Project Management like Maven, etc.</li>
                    <li>Successful development of EHRflex. Currently in charge of improvement and maintenance.</li>
                  </ul>
                </g:HTMLPanel>
              </g:DisclosurePanel>
            </td>
          </tr>
        </table>
       </g:HTMLPanel>
       
      <g:HTMLPanel ui:field="inormePanel">
        <table class='{style.ov_table}'>
          <tr>
            <td><a href="http://www.inorme.com" target="_blank">INORME</a> stands for Informatics, Organization and Methods. It was a Consulting, Systems Integration, Outsourcing and Software and Solutions Development Company. The main function of the company was to offer its services to the financial market: banks, savings banks, insurance companies and other financial companies.</td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
            <td>
              <g:DisclosurePanel ui:field="respInormeDiscPanel">
                <g:header>Responsibilities:</g:header>
                <g:HTMLPanel>
                  <ul>
                    <li>Software development for the financial market, using COBOL, Visual Basic in Bull Systems with Gcos and IBM.</li>
                    <li>Software development in Products Development Department in CAM (Mediterranean savings bank).</li>
                  </ul>
                </g:HTMLPanel>
              </g:DisclosurePanel>
            </td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
            <td>
              <g:DisclosurePanel ui:field="achievInormeDiscPanel">
                <g:header>Achievements:</g:header>
                <g:HTMLPanel>
                  <ul>
                    <li>Learned knowledge in financial field and different technologies such as COBOL, Visual Basic, hierarchical data bases.</li>
                  </ul>
                </g:HTMLPanel>
              </g:DisclosurePanel>
            </td>
          </tr>
        </table>
       </g:HTMLPanel>
      
      <g:HTMLPanel ui:field="teacherPanel">
        <table class='{style.ov_table}'>
          <tr>
            <td>Taught the main programs of Microsoft Office Package: Word, Access and Excel. The course was addressed to unemployed people, from under age to elderly.</td>
          </tr>
        </table>
      </g:HTMLPanel>
      
      <g:HTMLPanel ui:field="hospitalPanel">
        <table class='{style.ov_table}'>
          <tr>
            <td>The project was supervised by the AVS (Valencian Health Agency). The main goal was to satisfy the clinicians´ needs with the management of every document in the hospital. It involved development of a data base and a web interface acting as a catalog for the documents.</td>
          </tr>
        </table>
      </g:HTMLPanel>
      
      </g:HTMLPanel>
      </g:ScrollPanel>

</ui:UiBinder> 